[
	{ "question": "bright/light", "answer": "あかるい" },
	{ "question": "the day after tomorrow", "answer": "あさって" },
	{ "question": "warm", "answer": "あたたかい" },
	{ "question": "hot", "answer": "あつい" },
	{ "question": "(my) elder brother", "answer": "あに" },
	{ "question": "(my) elder sister", "answer": "あね" },
	{ "question": "rain", "answer": "あめ" },
	{ "question": "busy", "answer": "いそがしい" },
	{ "question": "together", "answer": "いっしょうに" },
	{ "question": "always", "answer": "いつも" },
	{ "question": "meaning", "answer": "いみ" },
	{ "question": "(my) younger sister", "answer": "いもうと" },
	{ "question": "(your. his) younger sister", "answer": "いもうとさん" },
	{ "question": "playground/field", "answer": "うんどうじょう" },
	{ "question": "movie", "answer": "えいが" },
	{ "question": "picture postcard", "answer": "えはがき" },
	{ "question": "How are you?", "answer": "おげんきですか" },
	{ "question": "(your, his)wife", "answer": "おくさん" },
	{ "question": "(your, his)daughter", "answer": "おじょうさん" },
	{ "question": "(my)husband", "answer": "おっと" },
	{ "question": "sound/noise", "answer": "おと" },
	{ "question": "father", "answer": "おとうさん" },
	{ "question": "(my) younger brother", "answer": "おとうと" },
	{ "question": "(your, his) younger brother", "answer": "おとうとさん" },
	{ "question": "the day before yesterday", "answer": "おととい" },
	{ "question": "the year before last", "answer": "おととし" },
	{ "question": "elder brother", "answer": "おにいさん" },
	{ "question": "elder sister", "answer": "おねえさん" },
	{ "question": "get off", "answer": "おります" },
	{ "question": "family", "answer": "かぞく" },
	{ "question": "form/shape", "answer": "かたち" },
	{ "question": "easy", "answer": "かんたん" },
	{ "question": "can hear/hear", "answer": "きこえます" },
	{ "question": "yesterday", "answer": "きのう" },
	{ "question": "brothers and sisters", "answer": "きょうだい" },
	{ "question": "last year", "answer": "きょねん" },
	{ "question": "this morning", "answer": "けさ" },
	{ "question": "healthy/vigorous", "answer": "げんき" },
	{ "question": "(senior) highschool student", "answer": "こうこうせい" },
	{ "question": "voice", "answer": "こえ" },
	{ "question": "(your, his) family", "answer": "こかぞく" },
	{ "question": "(your, his) sibling", "answer": "ごきょうだい" },
	{ "question": "(your, her) husband", "answer": "ごしゅじん" },
	{ "question": "this year", "answer": "ことし" },
	{ "question": "word/language", "answer": "ことば" },
	{ "question": "the other day", "answer": "このまえ" },
	{ "question": "husband and wife", "answer": "ごふうふ" },
	{ "question": "(your, his)parents", "answer": "ごりょうしん" },
	{ "question": "this months", "answer": "こんげつ" },
	{ "question": "concert", "answer": "コンサート" },
	{ "question": "this week", "answer": "こんしゅう" },
	{ "question": "tonight", "answer": "こんや" },
	{ "question": "soccer", "answer": "サッカー" },
	{ "question": "cold/chilly", "answer": "さむい" },
	{ "question": "the month after next", "answer": "さらいげつ" },
	{ "question": "the week after next", "answer": "さらいしゅう" },
	{ "question": "the year after next", "answer": "さらいねん" },
	{ "question": "regrettable/sorry", "answer": "ざんねん" },
	{ "question": "game/match", "answer": "しあい" },
	{ "question": "test/examination", "answer": "しけん" },
	{ "question": "oneself", "answer": "じぶん" },
	{ "question": "(my)husband", "answer": "しゅじん" },
	{ "question": "elementary schoolchild", "answer": "しょうがくせい" },
	{ "question": "bullet train", "answer": "しんかんせん" },
	{ "question": "cool", "answer": "すずしい" },
	{ "question": "sports", "answer": "スポーツ" },
	{ "question": "last month", "answer": "せんげつ" },
	{ "question": "last week", "answer": "せんしゅう" },
	{ "question": "the month before the last", "answer": "せんせんげつ" },
	{ "question": "the week before the last", "answer": "せんせんしゅう" },
	{
		"question": "that's good/it was lucky of you",
		"answer": "それはよかったですね"
	},
	{ "question": "embassy", "answer": "たいしかん" },
	{ "question": "pleasant/fun", "answer": "たのしい" },
	{ "question": "(my) father", "answer": "ちち" },
	{ "question": "(my) wife", "answer": "つま" },
	{ "question": "t shirt", "answer": "チーシャツ" },
	{ "question": "tennis", "answer": "テニス" },
	{ "question": "weather", "answer": "てんき" },
	{ "question": "when", "answer": "とき" },
	{ "question": "sometimes", "answer": "ときどき" },
	{ "question": "somewhere", "answer": "どうか" },
	{ "question": "place", "answer": "ところ" },
	{ "question": "very", "answer": "とても" },
	{ "question": "friend", "answer": "ともだち" },
	{ "question": "what kind of (sports)", "answer": "どんな" },
	{ "question": "what sort of/what(does it)look like", "answer": "どんな" },
	{ "question": "news", "answer": "ニュース" },
	{ "question": "carrot", "answer": "にんじん" },
	{ "question": "stand/kiosk", "answer": "ばいてん" },
	{ "question": "field/farm", "answer": "はたけ" },
	{ "question": "badminton", "answer": "バドミントン" },
	{ "question": "(my)mother", "answer": "はは" },
	{ "question": "piano", "answer": "ピアノ" },
	{ "question": "free(time)", "answer": "ひま" },
	{ "question": "ping-pong", "answer": "ピンポン" },
	{ "question": "husband and wife", "answer": "ふうふ" },
	{ "question": "winter", "answer": "ふゆ" },
	{ "question": "every week", "answer": "まいしゅう" },
	{ "question": "can see/see", "answer": "みえます" },
	{ "question": "road", "answer": "みち" },
	{ "question": "the past/the old days", "answer": "むかし" },
	{ "question": "(my)son", "answer": "むすこ" },
	{ "question": "(your, his) son", "answer": "むすこさん" },
	{ "question": "(my)daughter", "answer": "むすめ" },
	{ "question": "baseball", "answer": "やきゅう" },
	{ "question": "baseball ground", "answer": "やきゅうじょう" },
	{ "question": "closed/holiday/absence", "answer": "やすみ" },
	{ "question": "last night", "answer": "ゆうべ" },
	{ "question": "kindergarden", "answer": "ゆうちえん" },
	{ "question": "well", "answer": "よく" },
	{ "question": "next month", "answer": "らいげつ" },
	{ "question": "next week", "answer": "らいしゅう" },
	{ "question": "next year", "answer": "らいねん" },
	{ "question": "dormitory", "answer": "りょう" },
	{ "question": "(my) parents", "answer": "りょうしん" },
	{ "question": "rule", "answer": "ルール" },
	{ "question": "understand", "answer": "わかります" }
]
